[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of criminal was John Dillinger, a historical figure and leading character in the 2009 Public Enemies movie?", "correct_answer": "Bank robber", "incorrect_answers": ["Forger", "Rapist", "Murderer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the most recommended activity that helps prevent or fight obesity.", "correct_answer": "Getting exercise", "incorrect_answers": ["Quitting alcohol", "Eating salads only", "Drinking a lot of water"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This day in April is celebrated as Earth Day in many countries.", "correct_answer": "22", "incorrect_answers": ["31", "12", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The voice of Piglet on many Winnie the Pooh programs, this actor played juror #2 in the movie 12 Angry Men.", "correct_answer": "John Fiedler", "incorrect_answers": ["Lee J. Cobb", "Joseph Sweeney", "Martin Balsam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What incredible occupation does Jessica Langes character, Carmen, have in the 2005 dramedy movie Broken Flowers?", "correct_answer": "Animal communicator", "incorrect_answers": ["Flower whisperer", "Animal mortician", "Flower chef"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Two angles of a triangle are 4 degrees and 56 degrees, respectively. How large is the  third angle?", "correct_answer": "120 degrees", "incorrect_answers": ["60 degrees", "45 degrees", "30 degrees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You have just laid down your entire hand in matched sets of four card books by taking cards from another player. What game have you just won?", "correct_answer": "Go Fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Gin Rummy", "Rummy 500", "War"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saruman the White is an enemy of Sauron, the main villain of The Lord of the Rings trilogy.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On which of the Canary Islands is the Mount Teide volcano located?", "correct_answer": "Tenerife", "incorrect_answers": ["Gran Canaria", "Fuerteventura", "La Palma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It has been shown that people with diabetes are less likely to have a heart attack if they take a cholesterol-lowering medication, even if their cholesterol level is perfectly normal already.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What car is Robbie saving for in the popular movie Dirty Dancing?", "correct_answer": "Alpha Romeo", "incorrect_answers": ["Cadillac", "Limo", "Mercedes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What model of robot does Arnold Schwarzenegger play in the Terminator series?", "correct_answer": "T-101", "incorrect_answers": ["T-100", "T-1000", "T-1001"]}]